<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Golden Blog-A-Thon</title>
    <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Golden Blog-A-Thon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 09:50:10 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Dream, An Awakening</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/dream_alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 09:50:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/dream_alive/</guid>
      <description>In a world where support is everything, value for value is there to help
Gruezi, one and all! Welcome back! Not much in the way of sats support this week, which is a-okay to me, just being transparent! Before we begin, I have some corrections to make to a previous article, The Golden Tech Stack:
Corrections A Initially, I stated that (some liberties here):
I will be running a start9 node for the blog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s All According To Plan (but not mine)</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/comingalong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 19:08:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/comingalong/</guid>
      <description>It seems that the tooling was there, I am just not well versed in Google Fu.
The Value Train is Coming! Welcome one and all! Value for Value is here in blog land and it was right before our eyes. It seems the tooling was there, I am just not well versed in Google-Fu! BeardedTek has figured out how to get boosts working (WITH A MODAL SCREEN!!!) with Alby. This is very exciting, as it seems that with this same tooling, I can get the BTCPayServer going with this modal button as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/goldentechstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 19:45:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/goldentechstack/</guid>
      <description>#The Golden Tech Stack
Welcome Time is lovely, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? It just flows on like a river. Anyway, some stuff has changed and an update is due! I hope you are well and excited for another edition of my blog.
This edition of the blog, I asked a simple question to my bitcoiner pals over at the Jupiter Broadcasting Matrix channel: &amp;ldquo;What would you like to see me write about or have my opinion on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V4Va la Revolucion!</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/v4v/letsgoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:29:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/v4v/letsgoo/</guid>
      <description>A Very Warm Thanks Thank you. For those of you that sent a few sats, it is much appreciated. Even if for a meme or because you believe the dream, it means the world to me.
Unfortunately, for me, I am more of a thinker and a logistics guy than a super talented coder. Coding makes me want to have a headbutt contest with a wall and see who taps out first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textual Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/textualboardmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/textualboardmeeting/</guid>
      <description>The Only Board Meeting Where Clothes Are Optional Welcome, dear reader! Welcome to what I feel could be a new era. An era of potentially unexplored territory! I have googled far and wide and haven&amp;rsquo;t seen too much of this comcept for this medium, and maybe its called something else entirely. What am I speaking about, you ask?
Value for Value This is a model that allows for much more than the traditional &amp;ldquo;Here&amp;rsquo;s some money because I enjoy your content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promised an Update</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/medupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:15:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/medupdate/</guid>
      <description>What a Whirlwind Hello again! So, I promiosed a post-appointment update and here we are.
According to my mental health doctor, she had no idea that my refills were being ignored. I followed protocol, etc.
Tl;dr, was able to get my refills taken care of and I am in a much better state than I was this morning.
So, what happened? That, is the real question. While I don&amp;rsquo;t like self-diagnosing, what I found was that I was suffering from Antidepressant Discontinuation Syndrome</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctors and Meds and Failures, Oh My</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/butwhy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 06:26:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/butwhy/</guid>
      <description>The Fallacy Welcome, once again to my blog, where I sometimes muse over non-technical topics and ask for advice.
This morning, that question is this: What are some ways that you have dealt with depression?
I&amp;rsquo;ll be fairly candid with you - I have a very hard time dealing with myself sometimes. I never really learned great coping mechanisms and had some incredible hardships before I was 21. For the last (I think?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s almost the end of July, Dragon.</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/morebizstuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 19:03:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/morebizstuff/</guid>
      <description>What Is Up, Gamers? As one of my old favorite YouTubers used to say, &amp;ldquo;Whadizuuuuuup?&amp;rdquo; TGD coming at you with another candid update!
The last couple weeks have been pretty challenging as far as business and figuring out new processes. We have had some electrical issues plague us and machine issues, bleh. BUT, I have a small update!
I ordered coffee, not tea! Well, hope you like Earl Grey, cause, I have some updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anothermadmuser</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/anothermadmuser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 17:35:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/anothermadmuser/</guid>
      <description>A Very Happy Hello to You All! Well, hello there! How have you all been doing? Sitting and doing blogging hasn&amp;rsquo;t been my forte, but, one day I hope to get much better at it. I would have hoped that this would have been a weekly thing, but, alas, I let things get away from me.
Have you been programming? The long and short is: unfortunately, no. I get really overwhelemed learning coding for some reason at it looks very daunting to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dream, A Failure</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/bizishard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 20:30:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/bizishard/</guid>
      <description>Mental Anguish, Physical Pseudo Prowess Hello, Dear Reader! Welcome back to my humble blog! Its been a hectic month or two since I posted last, but, here we are! I finally got off my laurels and started my side business&amp;rsquo; website with my domain host over at Kitterman Creative. Check us out if you need some 3D Printed goodness or some custom stuff for whatever! I wish that I could go on and on about how good its doing, but, we have but one repeat customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ponderpotent</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/ponderpotent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:10:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/ponderpotent/</guid>
      <description>Another Week, Another Post Ponderances Beyond I sit and ponder another week of work and wonder, am I headed down the right path?
How&amp;rsquo;s it going, folks? Here I sit, engineering a fitting I accidentally broke on my CR10S Pro v2 and wonder, is all this right? Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, everything is going fairly well (knock on wood), but, I always wonder if I am headed down the right path, y&amp;rsquo;know?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyrics and Me</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/lyricsandme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 17:36:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/lyricsandme/</guid>
      <description>New Week, New Post Well, hello there! Glad to be making you a new post, dear reader! I sincerly hope your week went well and you accomplished or set a goal or two! It has definitely been a week of trials and tribulations in my camp, but, I continue on. I am re-starting my efforts to run my own Jellyfin server again for my house, so, there is that! The setup was much easier than previous efforts, but, we will see if it stays connected or stops a bunch this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Thoughts on Linux</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/mythoughtsonlinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 20:35:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/mythoughtsonlinux/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Time Ah, yes. A new week and a new blog has yet to be written. Heck, I still have some cars to make for next weeks Race. But, before that, I have some thoughts and opinions!
But, the Race Wrap-Up! Fine, fine. Tl;Dr, I took second and third in the race. We did King of the Hill style with eight cars and I got four in, three after the challenge was issued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Day Woes</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/racedaywoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:25:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/racedaywoes/</guid>
      <description>Race Day Sunday, sunDAY, SUNDAY! The day I love and dread all at once. A few months ago, I took up diecast collecting and modifying.
Excuse the mess..
It has been a blast! With the modifying, came the racing of them as well. Axel swaps from stock to nickel-plated or just faster wheels. It was all pretty exciting!
A New Dawn I went to my first race day and was explained how it works</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warm Evenings, Warmer Posts</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/14aug22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 22:18:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/14aug22/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Back I sincerly hope you enjoyed reading my first post! Since my first post, I have learned a couple things:
I had not secured my site on Netlify (oops) Securing it was very easy after I got it going Git was much easier than I originally thought These all seem like very integral lessons to me! I think I may have had a breakthrough in what I would consider for my ultimate goal: SysAdmin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps into a Bright New World</title>
      <link>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/firststepsnewworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 20:27:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goldenblogathon.com/posts/firststepsnewworld/</guid>
      <description>A Hopeful Intro in a Dim World One man on a simple mission: to find his path forward and out of the Air Capital and into a tech-filled world.
Hello World, my name is Mick. I&amp;rsquo;m a 30 year old and have a simple, yet grandiose dream: get my FOSS-loving self a job in tech.
A Little About Me I have been grinding out non-career jobs for over a decade and went to school for Information Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
